HURRY. THE FLIGHT LEAVES
IN FOUR HOURS.
IT COULD TAKE TIME
TO GET A TAXI.
THERE COULD BE TRAFFIC.
THE PLANE COULD LEAVE EARLY.
COME ON!
SIX-HOUR TRIP TO LONDON.
THAT'S A LOT OF MONICA.
PASSPORT. CHECK.
CAMERA. CHECK.
TRAVELER'S CHECKS. CHECK.
WHO ARE YOU
SAYING CHECK TO?
MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, FOR REMEMBERING
TO PACK THE THING.
YOU KNOW, YOU DO A GOOD THING,
YOU GET A CHECK.
MY MOM DOES IT.
I NEVER REALIZED IT WAS WEIRD.
HEY, MY MOM USED TO PUT
HER HEAD IN THE OVEN.
ACTUALLY, SHE ONLY DID IT
THE ONE TIME
BUT IT WAS PRETTY WEIRD.
HEY.
ARE YOU READY YET?
YEP. TICKETS?
GOT THEM RIGHT HERE. CHECK.
IT'S ALL LONDON, BABY.
HERE WE GO.
YOU GOT YOUR PASSPORT?
YEAH. IN MY THIRD DRAWER
IN MY DRESSER.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE THAT.
OH!
THERE IT IS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
THE GARBAGE BAGS
ARE NEXT TO THE REFRIGERATOR.
RACHEL'S GOING TO BE HERE.
CAN'T I JUST ASK HER THIS STUFF?
YEAH, OKAY, GIVE THAT A TRY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
YEAH, CHEERIO.
LONDON, BABY.
OKAY, 'CAUSE THAT'S NOT GOING
TO GET ANNOYING.
LONDON, BABY!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS WRONG.
WELL, WE'RE ALL HERE.
WE SHOULD
GET GOING.
OH, I WANT TO COME OVER THERE
AND GIVE YOU A HUG
AND WISH YOU LUCK
ON YOUR WEDDING
BUT I CAN'T GET UP.
I'LL COME HUG YOU.
GREAT, YEAH. COULD YOU
BRING ME THE NEWSPAPER?
YEAH.
HAVE A GREAT WEDDING.
CHANDLER,
I WANT TO HUG YOU, TOO.
HEY.
AND YOU MIGHT AS WELL
BRING ME MY BOOK.
IT'S ON THE COUNTER
IN YOUR APARTMENT.
OH.
SO, WE'RE OFF.
HAVE FUN.
THANKS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE THERE.
I KNOW.
SO, SO, SO COME.
WHY DON'T YOU COME?
WHAT?
TO LONDON.
COME TO LONDON, PLEASE.
IT WOULD MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
I GOT TO WORK.
I'M SORRY.
WHY CAN'T YOU TAKE
A COUPLE OF DAYS OFF?
BECAUSE I CAN'T, ROSS.
I TOLD YOU, NO, I CAN'T.
THIS IS MY WEDDING.
NOW WE ARE LATE.
LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
LET'S GO!
FINE. YOU'LL...
YOU'LL WATCH IT ON VIDEO
WHEN WE GET BACK.
HERE YOU GO, PHOEBE.
HERE YOU GO, PHO-BO,
PHOO-BILA, PHEE-BE-BOO.
THANK YOU.
( giggles )
YOU.
( laughing )
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO.
BYE, PHEEBS.
BYE.
LONDON, BABY!
OH, GOD.
OH, DO YOU NEED A HUG?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BRING ME ANYTHING.
♪ LONDON CALLING ♪
♪ YES, I WAS THERE, TOO ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAID? ♪
♪ WELL, SOME OF IT WAS TRUE ♪
♪ LONDON CALLING. ♪
ALL RIGHT, CHANDLER,
DO SOMETHING.
COME ON
I AM. I'M IGNORING YOU.
I'M GOING TO BE
THE ON-CAMERA GUY.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST STOP:
WESTMINSTER ABBEY.
OH, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
THAT'S LONDON, BABY.
ALL RIGHT,
THE HOTEL'S HERE.
WAIT.
NO. WE WANT TO GO...
NO.
I KNOW.
I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO GO INTO THE MAP.
OKAY, IF YOU SEE
A LITTLE VERSION OF ME IN THERE
KILL IT.
I GOT IT.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, LISTEN, LISTEN.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE
TO WALK THIS WAY
THE ENTIRE TIME, ARE WE?
SHH.
OH, MAN, YOU MADE ME LOSE IT.
AND THAT WAS
ALL BEFORE 10:00.
THE CATERER RANG TO SAY
IT'S GOING TO BE CHICKEN KIEV
INSTEAD OF CHICKEN TARRAGON.
AND THEN THE FLORIST
PHONED TO SAY
THAT THERE AREN'T
ANY TULIPS
AND THEN THE CELLIST
HAS CARPAL TUNNEL SYNDROME.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
EMILY, HONEY, OKAY.
WELL, UP YOURS, TOO.
WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS.
NO, NO.
THAT'S TIME-OUT.
SORRY.
SWEETIE, YOU
GOT TO RELAX.
EVERYTHING'S GOING
TO BE GREAT, OKAY?
COME ON, COME ON.
CHICKEN KIEV?
MM-HMM.
DOESN'T THAT
SOUND DELICIOUS?
I KNOW
BUT SOMETHING LIKE SALMON
WOULD BE SO MUCH MORE ELEGANT
THAN CHICKEN
AND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE SALMONELLA.
OH, GOD.
SO I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE WHERE
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
YES, YES.
THIS PLACE
IS BEAUTIFUL.
EMILY'S PARENTS
GOT MARRIED HERE.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE TEARING IT DOWN.
IT REALLY IS
THE MOST LOVELY BUILDING.
I MEAN, IT'S OVER...
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S NICE.
OH.
OH. OH, MY GOD.
HOW CAN THIS BE HAPPENING?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
EVERYTHING'LL
BE ALL RIGHT.
HOW?
UH-HUH, I SEE THAT.
I TALKED TO THE GUY
WITH THE SHOVEL
AND FOUND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
Both:
WHAT?
THEY TORE IT DOWN
A FEW DAYS EARLY.
ALL RIGHT,
WESTMINSTER ABBEY.
HANDS DOWN,
BEST ABBEY I'VE EVER SEEN.
HEY.
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE ABBEY, CHANDLER?
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
THEY'RE THINKING OF CHANGING
THE NAME OF THIS PLACE.
REALLY? TO WHAT?
TO PUT THE CAMERA AWAY!
MAN, YOU ARE
WESTMINSTER CRABBY.
OH.
HONEY, DON'T GET UP.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
NOTHING.
I AM HERE TO TAKE CARE OF YOU.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
OKAY. I HAVE A WEDGIE.
OKAY, THAT IS ALL YOU.
SO...
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR LUNCH?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS WE HAVE TO EAT.
YEAH, I DO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I'M JUST BUMMED THE WAY
I LEFT THINGS WITH ROSS.
WISH I DIDN'T LIE TO HIM
ABOUT HAVING TO WORK.
SEEMS SO MAD AT ME.
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
IF SOMEONE I WAS STILL
IN LOVE WITH WAS...
STILL IN LOVE WITH?
YEAH.
I'M NOT IN LOVE WITH ROSS.
OH.
NO, NO. GOOD.
ME NEITHER.
PHOEBE, I'M NOT GOING
TO ROSS' WEDDING
BECAUSE HE'S MY EX-BOYFRIEND
AND THAT WOULD BE
REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
NOT BECAUSE I'M STILL
IN LOVE WITH HIM.
I MEAN, HEY, YOU KNOW, I LIKE
ROSS AS MUCH AS THE NEXT GUY.
I MEAN, CLEARLY,
I HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM
BUT FEELINGS DON'T MEAN LOVE.
DO I STILL HAVE LOVING FEELINGS
FOR ROSS?
YEAH!
BUT I HAVE CONTINUING
FEELINGS OF LOVE
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE
SEXUAL FEELINGS FOR HIM
BUT I DO LOVE HIM.
( gasps )
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY...
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?!
W-WE THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
"WE"?
WE TALK ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME.
YOU ALL KNOW.
DOES ROSS KNOW?
OH, NO.
ROSS DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME!
WELL, 'CAUSE
WE THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
GOD, IT, IT WOULD BE LIKE,
YOU KNOW, TELLING MONICA
"HEY, YOU KNOW,
YOU LIKE THINGS CLEAN."
HI.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
FINE GENTLEMEN
IN THE MARKET FOR?
WE GOT SCARVES
SOUVENIR
POSTCARDS...
CHECK THIS OUT, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S THE STUFF.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'M NOT GOING
TO HAVE TO BUY
THAT "I'M WITH STUPID"
T-SHIRT ANYMORE.
WELL, I LIKE IT.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE NOT REALLY
GOING TO BUY THAT.
YOU'VE EMBARRASSED ME
ENOUGH FOR ONE DAY.
OH, I EMBARRASS YOU?
HOW CAN I ANSWER THAT
WHEN I'M PRETENDING
I DON'T KNOW YOU?
HE'S JUST JEALOUS.
YOU'LL FIT RIGHT IN.
ALL LONDONERS WEAR THEM.
OH, REALLY?
THEN HOW COME
NO ONE HERE ANYWHERE
IS WEARING ONE?
THEY'RE
ALL TOURISTS.
YEAH.
LOOK, IF YOU INSIST
ON WEARING THAT IN PUBLIC
YOU'RE GOING TO SPEND
THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON
ALL BY YOURSELF.
OH, YEAH?
IF YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE ME CHOOSE
BETWEEN YOU AND THE HAT,
I CHOOSE THE HAT.
GOOD CHOICE.
THANKS.
OKAY, LOOK...
I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'M NOT GOING
TO BE EMBARRASSED ANYMORE.
HELLO?
HEY, I JUST SPOKE TO YOUR DAD
AND HE THINKS
WE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIND A NEW PLACE
FOR THE WEDDING.
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
WH-WH-WHAT,
YOU FOUND A PLACE?
NO, BUT MONICA
AND I WERE TALKING
AND-AND I WAS SO UPSET ABOUT
THE HALL BEING KNOCKED DOWN
AND SHE SUGGESTED
THAT WE JUST PUT THE WEDDING OFF
FOR A BIT.
SHE SAID WHAT?
SHE SAID IF I'M NOT HAPPY
GETTING MARRIED SOMEWHERE
THAT WE CAN FIND IN A DAY
WE SHOULD JUST POSTPONE IT.
( chuckles )
POSTPONE IT?
EMILY, DO YOU THINK
MONICA REALIZES
HOW MUCH OUR PARENTS SPENT
ON THIS WEDDING, HUH?
DO YOU THINK MY SISTER'S TEENY,
TINY, LITTLE BRAIN COMPREHENDS
THAT PEOPLE TOOK TIME
OUT OF THEIR LIVES
TO FLY THOUSANDS OF MILES
TO BE HERE, HUH?
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
LOOK, I REALIZE
THAT PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO BE
DISAPPOINTED...
( chuckles wryly )
BUT THEY'LL COME BACK
WHEN WE CAN DO IT RIGHT.
WELL, I CAN'T ASK PEOPLE
TO DO THAT.
WOULD YOU ASK PEOPLE
TO DO THAT?
DON'T YOU POINT
YOUR PANTS AT ME.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
ANYWHERE HALF-DECENT
WILL HAVE BEEN
BOOKED MONTHS AGO.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS OUR WEDDING
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THE ONLY THING I UNDERSTAND
IS POSTPONING IT
IS NOT AN OPTION.
THIS IS WHEN
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
SO, YOU'RE SAYING
IT'S NOW OR NEVER?
NO, I'M SAYING IT'S NOW.
OR?
THERE'S NO "OR" IN MINE.
WHAT IS WRONG
WITH THESE PANTS?!
IT'S NOT THE PANTS,
IT'S YOU WHO'S BACKWARDS.
IF YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW IMPORTANT THIS IS TO ME
PERHAPS WE SHOULDN'T BE
GETTING MARRIED AT ALL.
WH... E-EMILY, NO. WAIT.
STOP. EMILY, PLEA...
( shrieks )
HEY.
SO, DID SHOPPING
HELP YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
ABOUT ROSS?
MANHATTAN DOES NOT HAVE
ENOUGH STORES.
WELL, I THINK
I CAN HELP YOU
GET OVER HIM.
YOU CAN?
YEAH. I JUST NEED
YOU TO BRING ME
SOME PHOTOS OF ROSS,
AND A SMALL PIECE OF CHOCOLATE
AND A GLASS
OF TEPID WATER.
OOH, IS THIS ONE
OF THOSE THINGS
WHERE YOU THROW
A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF
IN A BAG
WITH SOME GRAVEYARD DIRT
AND THEN HANG IT
FROM A NORTH-FACING TREE?
ONLY IF YOU HAVE
THE HICCUPS, TOO.
YEAH, THE PICTURES
ARE FOR YOU.
THE CHOCOLATE
AND THE WATER'S FOR ME.
I JUST DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE GETTING UP.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
A PICTURE OF ROSS, OKAY?
AND YOU'RE GOING TO REMEMBER
ALL THE BAD THINGS ABOUT HIM.
ALL RIGHT? REALLY FOCUS
ON HIS FLAWS.
I CAN DO THAT.
I CERTAINLY DID THAT
WHILE WE WERE GOING OUT.
OKAY. HMM, BEFORE
WE GET STARTED
I JUST WANT TO SAY
FOR THE RECORD
THAT I LOVE ROSS.
I THINK HE'S
SUCH A GREAT GUY.
OKAY, NOW
CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND IMAGINE
THAT YOU'RE WITH ROSS.
OKAY, AND IMAGINE
THAT YOU'RE KISSING HIM
AND YOU'RE RUNNING YOUR HANDS
ALL OVER HIS BODY
AND THEN YOU RUN YOUR HANDS
THROUGH HIS HAIR
BUT, OH! EWW! GROSS!
IT'S SOME KIND OF GREASE.
IT'S GROSS!
HUH?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
HIS HAIR NEVER BOTHERED ME
THAT MUCH.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT WAS ALWAYS
MORE CRUNCHY THAN IT WAS GREASY.
OKAY.
THIS'LL BE HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT.
UM, LET'S TRY SOME
AVERSION THERAPY.
OKAY.
OKAY?
SO LOOK AT THE PICTURE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
AND, UM...
OW!
OKAY. HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW?
WELL, I LIKE YOU LESS.
HEY.
OH. SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID
THAT YOU WERE
EMBARRASSING ME.
THAT REALLY
WASN'T COOL.
IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER
I'VE HAD A
REALLY LOUSY DAY.
ME, TOO.
YEAH?
NO!
I HAD THE BEST DAY EVER.
DUDE, CHECK THIS OUT.
HEY!
SHH, SHH.
Say hi to my friend
and tell him you like my hat.
So what's your
friend's name?
Chandler.
Okay. So, hi, Chandler.
THAT... THAT WAS...
THAT'S FERGIE, BABY!
Joey says you don't
really like his hat
but I think it's
kind of dashing.
WHEN DID YOU...? HOW...?
I WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO GET TO BUCKINGHAM PALACE
SO I'M IN MY MAP, AND...
HEY.
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAD
A LITTLE TALK WITH EMILY.
YES, I DID.
AND YOU ARE WELCOME.
AM I?
AND WAS IT YOUR IDEA
TO POSTPONE THE WEDDING?
UM...
I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
WAIT UP.
HEY, HEY.
SINCE YOU'RE
THE FIX-IT LADY
HERE'S A PICKLE.
WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN THE BRIDE SAYS
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO HAVE
THE WEDDING AT ALL?
SHE SAID THAT?
YEAH.
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I TOLD HER IT WAS STUPID
TO PUT OFF THE WEDDING
JUST BECAUSE THE HALL WAS GONE
AND SHE LIKE FLIPPED OUT.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE EVEN DUMBER
THAN I AM.
EXCUSE ME?
ROSS, HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN PLANNING THIS WEDDING?
I DON'T KNOW. A MONTH.
EMILY HAS PROBABLY
BEEN PLANNING IT
SINCE SHE WAS FIVE--
EVER SINCE THE FIRST TIME
SHE TOOK A PILLOWCASE
AND HUNG IT OFF
THE BACK OF HER HEAD.
THAT'S WHAT WE DID.
WE DREAMED ABOUT
THE PERFECT WEDDING...
AND THE PERFECT PLACE...
WITH THE PERFECT
FOUR-TIERED
WEDDING CAKE...
WITH THE LITTLE
PEOPLE ON TOP.
BUT THE MOST
IMPORTANT PART
IS THAT WE HAD
THE PERFECT GUY
WHO UNDERSTOOD
JUST HOW IMPORTANT
ALL THAT OTHER STUFF WAS.
I HAD NO IDEA.
THAT PILLOWCASE THING?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE JUST DOING THE FLYING NUN.
SOMETIMES WE WERE.
COME ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO HELP ME
FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO, OKAY?
OKAY.
COME ON.
WELL, PRETTY
INTENSE, HUH?
YEAH.
HEY, I HOPE ROSS DIDN'T
THINK WE JUST WENT IN THERE
BECAUSE WE WERE
UNCOMFORTABLE
BEING OUT HERE.
I HOPE HE DID.
( phone ringing )
HELLO.
HEY, PHEEBS. IT'S JOEY.
HEY, JOEY. HEY, OH.
OH, I JUST SAW SOMEONE
THAT LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU
ON THE SUBWAY
AND I WAS GOING TO GO OVER
AND SAY HI
BUT THEN I FIGURED, HE
DOESN'T CARE HE LOOKS LIKE YOU.
THAT JUST COST ME FOUR BUCKS.
BUT, LISTEN, I JUST CALLED
TO SEE HOW THE CHICK
AND THE DUCK ARE DOING.
THEY'RE HAVING A GREAT TIME
WITH THEIR AUNT PHOEBE.
AUNT RACHEL
HASN'T BEEN
HELPFUL AT ALL.
SO DO YOU MISS ME?
KIND OF, BUT I'VE JUST
BEEN HAVING WAY TOO MUCH FUN.
OH, SO YOU'RE NOT HOMESICK YET?
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
THE SEVEN OF US MISS YOU.
WHO'S SEVEN?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
ME, RACHEL
THE BIRDS, THE BABIES.
AW, THE BABIES MISS ME?
( knocking )
PIZZA GUY'S HERE.
YOU ORDERED PIZZA WITHOUT ME?
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE WERE THINKING ABOUT YOU.
YOU KNOW, WE ORDERED
THE JOEY SPECIAL.
TWO PIZZAS?
( door closing )
YEP.
OKAY, GOT TO GO.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
WAIT. WHERE DID YOU GET IT FROM?
♪ ...Where everybody
knows your name ♪
( bouncy tune )
♪ And they're
always glad you came ♪
♪ You want to be
where you can see ♪
♪ Troubles are all the same ♪
♪ You want to be where
everybody knows your name. ♪
MONICA, WHY HAVE YOU
BROUGHT ME HERE
OF ALL PLACES?
YOU'LL SEE.
I TELL YOU, THIS WEDDING
IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
OH, GOD.
OKAY, BUT IMAGINE
A LOT MORE LIGHTS, OKAY?
AND... AND, YOU KNOW,
FEWER BRICKS, AND...
AND FLOWERS AND CANDLES.
AND THE MUSICIANS--
THEY CAN GO OVER HERE
AND THE CHAIRS--
THEY CAN FACE THIS WAY
AND...
YOU GO.
BUT... BUT IF YOU
DON'T LOVE THIS
THEN WE'LL DO IT
ANY OTHER PLACE, ANY OTHER TIME.
REALLY, IT'S FINE.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
IT'S PERFECT.
AND, I DON'T KNOW, IF
IT STARTS TO RAIN...
WELL, THEN WE'LL GET WET.
OH...
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A DATE.
Rachel:
PHEEBS?
YEAH?
YOU REMEMBER WHERE
THE DUCK FOOD IS?
IT'S IN THE GUYS' APARTMENT
UNDER THE SINK. WHY?
'CAUSE I'M GOING TO LONDON.
WHAT?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I HAVE TO TELL ROSS
THAT I LOVE HIM.
NOW, HONEY, YOU TAKE CARE.
YOU DON'T HAVE THOSE BABIES
TILL I GET BACK.
RACHEL, YOU CAN'T GO.
ROSS LOVES EMILY.
I KNOW. I KNOW HE DOES
BUT I HAVE TO TELL HIM
HOW I FEEL.
HE DESERVES TO HAVE
ALL OF THE INFORMATION
AND THEN HE CAN MAKE
AN INFORMED DECISION.
THAT'S NOT WHY YOU'RE GOING.
YOU'RE GOING BECAUSE YOU HOPE
HE'S GOING TO SAY
"YEAH, I LOVE YOU, TOO, RACH.
FORGET ABOUT THAT
BRITISH CHIPPY."
DO YOU THINK HE WILL?
NO, BECAUSE HE'S IN LOVE
WITH THE BRITISH CHIPPY.
RACHEL, IF YOU GO
YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO MESS WITH HIS HEAD
AND RUIN HIS WEDDING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU MISSED YOUR CHANCE.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THIS MUST
BE REALLY HARD.
IT'S OVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? NO.
IT'S NOT OVER
UNTIL SOMEONE SAYS, "I DO."
I DO.
I DO. I DO.
I DO! I DO!
( groans )
YEAH, LIKE I CAN
REALLY CHASE YOU.
I'M CARRYING A LITTER.